Hi, Guys.  So, now I have
arrived at the location at the Rafles Hotel.
I arrived earlier because
L happened to have work before me.  So
he arrived later.  So now
we are waiting.  He said he had already
gone upstairs.
Hello,
long life, the person is sought after.  There is.
O.   We're going to do
food testing later, guys.
Yes, but sorry, I went in
earlier.  I've already tasted it.
Kaji, sorry, I'm leaving your bag with you.  Now we
want to see what the fit is
today.  Let's go.  Can't wait.
Let's go.
[music]
Hi guys, welcome back to our YouTube
channel.  So today I've finished getting
ready to go to Task Food for
my and L's wedding. I'm really excited.
I'll meet L there later.
E so later I think he
will train to deliver it.  Well, I was
actually ready, but there was something I
missed.  I forget.  I haven't brushed my
teeth yet.  Oh my God, how can you brush your
teeth?  Forgot the most important thing.  So
now I really want to get my teeth done,
guys.
Guys, it turns out that wedding preparations involve
a lot of coordination and talking
with vendors, family members, and
other partners.
Before continuing with the vlog, I want to give you some
tips and tricks for those of you who are not confident
about bad breath.  Don't you want
your activities to be disturbed because your mouth isn't
fresh?
[music]
Well, the first step is brushing your teeth.
After that, double cleansing is mandatory using
Listerin mouthwash watermelon mint.  This
tastes very tropical, light,
not spicy in the mouth.  The vibes are
fun, perfect for daily refreshment
to boost your confidence.  [music]
It's finished.  Now I'm ready to go.
Okay, guys.  Now we have arrived at the
food test room.
Food testing.
You can see that this is really intentional.
It's like you've really been buffed up for the
big day.
Oh, this really is like a
full buffet.
Yes
Uh,
like this.  Later
the position will be like this.  There is
white rice, there is zoo fried rice, fried
Hong Kong noodles.
What is this?
broccoli.  Uh,
here's brown cereal, prown mayonnaise
and beef molan sal honey glicken.  So,
this was deliberately squeezed in
with our arrival so that everything was still fresh
.  And it looks good.  To be
honest, I've been trying out [music] in
installments because I'm hungry.
So I just tasted my ex.
Very delicious.
After a while, Siifa was already hungry
too.  Let's just get started.  E
food testing today.
Let's go, okay?
[music]
This is really interesting.  L s
yeah
I'll be like I'm going to waste it if I
don't.  Soup me too who was I?
Mixed cheese.  This is mushroom soup.
What's the name of the mixed cheese?  The meat is
there.
Oh, this is the same as the one my mother took.  Oh, one
spoonful later, okay?
Now let's be alone for now, okay?   We haven't
bribed each other on the wedding dais yet.
More like spilled.  More
spilled.
Yes  Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Hmm.  Nice.  Hmm.
This Ngobet is delicious with Padang rice, right?  No
way.
Wrong time.
Bread is also delicious.
It's not too
mushroomy, isn't it?  Hey.
And not too thick.
Thank you.  That's perfect.
Guys, that's how it works, people say
he uses bread, guys.
To be full, we usually use rice
when we're testing food.
Why is it
okay to add more food during the test?
Yes, it's
okay, try it, usually
people eat like this, the stems are
not per, don't just finish them
when you're full.   It's
delicious that
you protested that you couldn't get the package.  E
can be done if you make a living.
Don't be the guys either.  Is Mrs. Bunga
offal?
Yes  [music]
Oh, what's up?  When you cut it, it
looks like there's
no bone.  Oh, there are no
bones anymore.  So if it's oxtail without bones,
it's fine if it's oxtail [laughs]
don't make jokes when you're not
serious,
so I think I'll just shut up for a while.
Seriously,
let's try this one first.  Oh, there are some
who use pink,
but I prefer blue, it's not soft.
Different times, different times.  Oh, it's
different this time.  Different times.
Now I want to take the main course.  You
have to restrain yourself because there is
still a lot of food.  So we were like yes, the
important thing is that we have tasted it.
Feeling.
The important thing is that I've felt it.
White rice doesn't taste good.
It seems like white rice is the same everywhere
, guys.  So we don't think we're
using white rice.
Oh what is he?  It's like vermicelli but why is there
so much?  vermicelli but thinner.
Let's cancel it today, okay?
Yes  What do you want?
What do you want?
Ahah.  It's really tiny.
This is
broccoli.   Do
you want the plates to be separated like that
, honey?  So
if there's a voice, I'll take the
two one
[music],
we have to do it all, guys.  So
bismillahirrahmanirrahim,
I hope [clears throat]
my stomach will be
strong,
fish skin
.
Yes, that's fish skin.
Oh, there are dumplings.  Eh, this is empting wonton.
These crackers are really cute, aren't they?  There are
no colorful crackers.
There aren't any colorful crackers,
what should we try?
What's on the plate like this?
[music]
Let's try it, Guys.   It's
deliciously crispy.
This is fried rice.
Bali [clears throat]
[music]
between these two I have fried rice.
The fried rice is
delicious.
This is honey glazed chicken.
Right to know which
hmm is
delicious.
I really like chickens
like this, the
sweet ones with flour.
This is just take a try, try it,
sis, here, mother, there is still some
meat or fruit,
it's delicious, black pepper, yes, black pepper,
eat black pepper, yes,
what was this, sauce, okay, take the sauce, there's not enough, there's a
lot of it
.
I'm okay, but I'm more of a
Berserker.  Hehe.
Chicken
doesn't
taste like gendar, right?  What was that?
I know, Sis.  Gender
crackers are
quite squid.
So this is the price of squid.
It's just sor
[music]
Singapore Laksa,
they say
Oh, I, that's the most delicious
laksa.
Well, I really like that.  Yes, yes, I ...  There are
still lots on
the menu, Guys.  Just you guys want to see it's
pretty famous.  We should try it first.
There was laksa, right? There was laksa, but after this, I
don't know what, but there was Singapore chili
crab and salmon
black ang [music] a
lot of
guys, I was full, but my favorite is
liwet rice because at that time, during Torik's wedding ceremony,
if I'm not mistaken, after the wedding ceremony, we had
liwat rice for lunch, and I added
a lot, I don't know whether it was because I was tired or
hungry, but it was really delicious, we had
liwet. At that time, we were just getting close, and
he was like, yeah, I ate a lot of silwat, he
said Torik.  Hehe.  Then,
if I'm not mistaken,
you ran out of food, so you went to the kitchen to
help cook, right?
Help cook
so they'll come back for dinner.
Then he seemed to be carrying software at that time,
so what a
shame for the parents.  That's right.   There's
no such thing anymore, you know, you
heat it up,
heat it up again, put it in the fridge again
[music]
this is the hero of this hotel, Guys.  It's only
here.  And this is one of the most
awaited ones.
How much difference is that?
Let's go.
Wow, this is Alaskan crab, Guys.  So he's
not an ordinary crab, but an Alaskan
crab.
Alaskan crab.
That's why the meat is thick.
Let's try.
I really want to finish this, but I ca
n't do it later because Minang doesn't.
That's right.
Nice.  It's really a champion, I
swear, I've been
here for so many times, this is the second time when
there's the chili kban, right when I'm always
full,
so it's like it never runs
out, it's actually the
first time I've come here, I immediately
tried this, yeah,
because this is when I first
checked the venue, we were
given
this free discount, and it's not free,
actually,
what is it like, if it's complimentary, it might be
free.
Yes, it's complementary.  This is still the
champion, right?
This is unique because it's rare
to find things like this that are
truly delicious.  You can be too
weird if you do it wrong.
So he tires and continues to crab.
This [music] base seems to be a steel tire.
Flood.  Flood.
So what is this?  What sauce?
Does the sauce taste like Padang sauce
?   Is
not that?  [laughs] It
's like some kind of sauce, but it's delicious.
Tomatoes, huh?  Like a tomato, it
looks like a tomato.  But it seems like
because he was given this coriander [cough], it smells
good.  Hehe.  This coriander smells good,
right?
Coriander leaves.
Huh?
Honestly, my
pants are already tight.
Honestly, I'm on a diet.  Honestly, I'm on a diet.  Honestly, it's
just from the doctor
[laughs]
who is 34 full [clears throat] yeah.
[music]
Here it's different, it's not classical,
so we deconstructed it.  So the shape is
like this in regular like this
so it's not layered directly like that.
Truly.  This is like a salmon bag,
so it's like a salmon bag, usually the
salmon is directly on the outside like that.
Usually, if it's classic, it's
like a salmon bag.
So it's not like
we eat it like this
.   Just
eat.  Eat, eat, eat.
[music]
I think that Sis Kak and Sis Syifa
both like dessert, I think that's
dessert.  So today there is the last e-menu,
later Sara will release the
signature menu, we will have some Starcard,
okay?
Wow.  Thank You.  Yes  The
same way, but different, does this mean something
similar?
Similar.
And he also has two choices of chili sauce.
So there are green chilies, [music] there are
also red chilies.   Does that
mean the dendeng batok doesn't
have any chili sauce on it?
Yes  No, not immediately so it
becomes crispy.   Did
you eat it earlier?
Oh, you'd
rather pass by, right?  Try it.
I have never.  Just because El had
praised this, I was curious.
Penya for me yeah.
Take it darling, take the stink
beans and take a bath [laughs] take the
stink beans' armpits first.
What kind of chili sauce is this?
Well, there is this Thai shrimp paste chili sauce
.
Yes, sorry, this one.  This one.
This is chili sauce.
This one is like onion chili sauce
.  Well, try it.  Don't eat
the petek on the day.  [laughs]
Be patient, be patient, talk to
people later.  [laughs]
Wait a minute.
It's still long.  Hm dear.
Sambilnyang is also
really spicy, isn't it?
Nice.
Oh.
[music]
So did you eat the pete or not?
Already.
Oh my God, I'm done with him.
It can bite,
man.  After this, we want to meet
people
again.  Hey, where's my pocket money, Beb?
Well, I always put it here.
That's why I always bring
this wherever I go because it's
really on point, practical.  He just stays like this
.
Yes, he has a hanger.   It's
really easy.
Hehe.  Here, just two or three sprays are enough to make it
fresh immediately.
Hmm, the culm is really good.  Fresh again.
Thank you.
Yes dear.  In short, your breath will be
fresh instantly anytime and anywhere.
So after this we can immediately continue the
meeting.   That's cool, huh?
Let's continue
our list.
Oh yes.  E we are not on the list
actually but we want you to try it.
Well, this is called Coffee Lua Sil Cup.
[music] So that's the ice cream with
broad coffee.  Hehe.
Then inside there is ice, eh coffee
jelly.  Cof.
Then the green one is avocado
mousse.
Hmm.
Means.
Yes  And that's how to eat it, you can
crush it.  So it can be
destroyed.  Correct.   So Nah
.  Oh.
Now.
Oh my, it's completely destroyed.
What do you mean [laughs]?  Here's how it is
.  What I mean is this, K. I mean the
same as Kasia.  Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry,
sorry.  It's like old [laughs] the
pony is destroyed.  It's too broken
, bro.   It is
okay.  It is okay.  Well, let's
try this, what's it called?  Hey,
everyone eats together.  So it's like an
iced coffee mocha.   The
aado is delicious.
Yes, there is avocado too.  So it's
sweet but not too sweet.  Nice.
Even though I don't like coffee.  I
don't mean coffee.  Oh.  Ah,
it feels balanced, huh?
Yes
The avocado isn't too
avocadoy either.
Correct.  Then ee cok e si coffe, that's why
people who don't eat or don't
drink coffe can also enjoy it.
Because he also likes light coffee.  So it's
not a very strong e.
Kofit.  That means only in the ice cream,
right?
Yes, it is true.  There's also ice jelly too
.
Jelly coffee underneath.  So it's like
Korean mixed with an Indonesian touch
.  Because the coffee is luangkes.
Well,
this is our bride.
Hello, Chef.
Well, this is Chef Andrew.  Chef who
today incas.
Well, if there are any shortcomings, just
chat directly with the chef.
Okay.  Well, today we just
finished the food testing event for
Kak L and Kak Sira's event.  Maybe it would be better if
we just review the
food we tried today.
For Japanese soba, I
heeh to be honest, I don't really
like medicine.  So I
don't know if
other people besides me
would want to eat soba as an
appetizer or not.
Well [clears throat] then we'll give you options,
okay?  Anyway, the one that we
immediately agreed with was the paper
sir tuna and fresh.
Okay,
our
soup is also okay.
How to make mushrooms?   Does the
E travel lack the aroma of
the travel?
[music]
Our food testing is over for
today.  Hopefully everyone who eats will
like our choice.  In our opinion, it's
delicious.   We
think it's delicious.  Actually,
what are we?  we have big tastes in food
.  It means that we are
trusted by the people around
us to value delicious food.  So,
God willing, this will definitely be delicious and
hopefully everyone will like it and the quality of
the food will be maintained until the event
is over.  And hopefully the event
runs smoothly and everyone
goes home with a full stomach and a
happy mood.
Thank you for watching our vlog today.
Bye bye.